Step 1: scroll  [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page for '[Demo] ScreenPilot self-marketing automation test #2'. The page shows the issue detai
Step 2: scroll  [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. The task requires me to scroll down to find the comment box at the bottom of the issue. C
Step 3: scroll  [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom of the visible area, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign up for free to
Step 4: find_and_click (1461, 936) [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom of the visible area, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign up for free to
Step 5: scroll  [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign up for free to join this conversat
Step 6: scroll  [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom of the visible area, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign up for free to
Step 7: scroll  [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom of the visible area, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign up for free to
Step 8: find_and_click (1021, 934) [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom of the visible area, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign up for free to
Step 9: scroll  [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign up for free to join this conversat
Step 10: scroll  [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom of the visible area, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign up for free to
Step 11: scroll  [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. Looking at the current screenshot, I can see the issue details with a table of screenshot
Step 12: find_and_click  [FAIL]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom of the visible area, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign up for free to
Step 13: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign
Step 14: scroll  [OK]\NI can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom of the visible area, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign up for free to
Step 15: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see a GitHub issue page. At the bottom, there's a yellow banner that says 'Sign